

CONTACT

- +37493142243
- +37495142240
- mesropyanarman21@gmail.com
- Armenia, Yerevan

SKILLS

- HTML/CSS
- SASS
- JAVASCRIPT
- TYPESCRIPT
- REACT.JS
- NEXT.JS
- REDUX
- GIT

LANGUAGES

- ARMENIAN [NATIVE]
- RUSSIAN [ADVANCED]
- ENGLISH [MEDIUM]

ARMAN MESROPYAN

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

PROFILE

I appreciate high-quality, competent work with teammates and an increased sense of responsibility in every job. Any new project motivates me gain new knowledge and experience

In work I rate highly`

- Honesty
- Teamwork
- Punctuality
- A responsibility
- Time management
- Interpersonal communication

WORK EXPERIENCE

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

ROCKET SYSTEMS

Jul.2023 - Now

• As a frontend developer at Rocket Systems, my primary focus is on developing applications using React.js and TypeScript, as well as creating mobile applications with React Native. React.js is a popular JavaScript library for building user interfaces, and TypeScript adds static typing to JavaScript, providing better code maintainability and catching errors early in the development process. n my role, I collaborate with the design and backend teams to translate user interface mockups and wireframes into fully functional and responsive web applications. I utilize my expertise in React.js and TypeScript to write clean, efficient, and modular code that adheres to industry best practices and coding standards.

FRONTEND DEVELOPMENT TUTOR

GROUP 404

Nov.2022 - Apr.2023

What am I doing here?

- I teach FrontEnd development
- HTML
- CSS
- SCSS/SASS
- Javascript

EDUCATION

SMART CODE

FRONTEND DEVELOPMENT

2021

YERVAN STATE COLLEGE OF INFORMATICS

SECONDARY SPECIALIZED EDUCATION

2014 - 2018

EVENTS

BUISSUP GLOBAL FORUM

2022

WE PARTICIPATED IN THE BISSUP GLOBAL FORUM PROJECT WITH A GREAT IDEA AND WON 1ST PLACE.

O FRONTEND DEVELOPER

GROUP 404

Apr.2022 - Apr.2023

What am I doing here?

- I work on react and typescript in different projects, mostly admin and not only.
- Implementing a responsive approach focused on mobile devices.
- Collaboration with product team members to implement a new feature
- Coordinating with the web development team to design user interfaces for client websites using JavaScript, TypeScript, React.JS. Developing and coding web applications for customer accounts, including debugging problems, diagnosing root causes, and identifying solutions.

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

SHARP BRAINS

Jan.2021 - Apr.2022

What did I do there?

- user interface development
- creating an adaptive application
- creating a functional application
- creating an HTML page of the site based on design layouts
- binding to the user interface of scripts that provide visualization
- and animation of the site pages;
- Development of Single Page Applications: React.js